Tufts University Prison Initiative of the Tisch College of Civic Life (TUPIT) ReSentencing Journal Submissions UA256
Tufts Archival Research Center
- 2022 accessions, circa 2020 -- 2021; UA256.000001; 679 Digital Object(s)
  - Elias, Craig, 2021 June 7 -- 2021 September 10; UA256.000241; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - The Gambler, 2021 June 7; UA256.000243; 1 Digital Object(s); 2.26 Megabytes
      Pennsylvania; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Short stories
  - Elizondo, Dustin, circa 2021; UA256.000244
    - Prison is a Gift, circa 2021; UA256.000245; 1 Digital Object(s); 54 Kilobytes
    - Words, circa 2021; UA256.000246; 1 Digital Object(s); 53 Kilobytes
  - Ellertson, Nathan, circa 2021; UA256.000247
    Vermont; Prisoners as artists -- United States
    - For My Beautiful Wife Kristy, circa 2021; UA256.000248; 1 Digital Object(s); 673 Kilobytes
      Vermont; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Essays
    - To My Family, circa 2021; UA256.000249; 1 Digital Object(s); 336 Kilobytes
  - Espinoza, Tim, 2021 June 13 -- 2021 September 7; UA256.000250; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Tired, 2021 June 13; UA256.000251; 1 Digital Object(s); 424 Kilobytes
    - Regrets, 2021 June 13; UA256.000252; 1 Digital Object(s); 171 Kilobytes
    - Prison, 2021 June 13; UA256.000253; 1 Digital Object(s); 94 Kilobytes
    - Gangster, 2021 June 13; UA256.000254; 1 Digital Object(s); 215 Kilobytes
    - Hope, 2021 June 13; UA256.000255; 1 Digital Object(s); 158 Kilobytes
  - Everett, Christopher D., 2021 June 1; UA256.000256; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - The introduction into an unknown impetus, 2021 June 1; UA256.000257; 1 Digital Object(s); 516 Kilobytes
  - Farrell, Thomas, circa 2021; UA256.000258
    - Living Together, circa 2021; UA256.000259; 1 Digital Object(s); 236 Kilobytes
  - Fernandez, Emilio C., 2021 June 7; UA256.000260; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Through the glass, 2021 June 7; UA256.000261
  - Ferriel, Thomas, 2021 May 22; UA256.000262
    Arkansas; Prisoners as artists -- United States
    - How My Life Was Impacted by Being Incarcerated, 2021 May 22; UA256.000263
      Arkansas; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Essays
  - Firman, Marco, circa 2021; UA256.000264
    - Maya a Bird, circa 2021; UA256.000265; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.6 Megabytes
      California; Prisoners as artists -- United States; watercolors (paintings)
    - Haiku, circa 2021; UA256.000266; 1 Digital Object(s); 14.3 Megabytes
  - Forbes, Auston, 2021 June 29; UA256.000267; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Still here, 2021 June 29; UA256.000268
    - Portrait of Feeling, 2021 June 29; UA256.000269
    - Intake, 2021 June 29; UA256.000270; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.83 Megabytes
    - Understanding, 2021 June 29; UA256.000271
    - Simon-19, 2021 June 29; UA256.000272
  - Foust, Kimya, 2021 June 4; UA256.000273; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Where I am from…, 2021 June 4; UA256.000274; 1 Digital Object(s); 815 Kilobytes
    - The Talking Object, 2021 June 4; UA256.000275; 1 Digital Object(s); 2.43 Megabytes
      Massachusetts; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Short stories
  - Harun Fox, circa 2021; UA256.000276
    - Cotton is King Again, circa 2021; UA256.000277
  - Fox, James, circa 2021; UA256.000278
    - Comic strip visual art, circa 2021; UA256.000279; 1 Digital Object(s); 23.7 Megabytes
  - Frescatore, Rusty, 2017 May 28 -- 2021; UA256.000280
    - If the walls could talk, 2017 May 28; UA256.000281; 1 Digital Object(s); 70 Kilobytes
  - Fuller, Brian, circa 2021; UA256.000282; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Just had to share, 2021 August 20; UA256.000283; 1 Digital Object(s); 271 Kilobytes
    - My Markers are Almost Dry, circa 2021; UA256.000284; 1 Digital Object(s); 596 Kilobytes
      Texas; Prisoners as artists -- United States; pen and ink drawings
    - Four flowers, circa 2021; UA256.000285; 1 Digital Object(s); 283 Kilobytes
    - Little scraps of paper, circa 2021; UA256.000286; 1 Digital Object(s); 455 Kilobytes
    - Never far away, circa 2021; UA256.000287; 1 Digital Object(s); 354 Kilobytes
    - Cellie, circa 2021; UA256.000288; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.59 Megabytes
      Texas; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Essays
  - Gabonia, Leo, 2021 May 21 -- 2021 June 15; UA256.000289; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - The Truth, 2021 May 21; UA256.000290; 1 Digital Object(s); 656 Kilobytes
    - Hatred of the Beast, 2021 May 21; UA256.000291; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.04 Megabytes
    - Leave the Troubled Water Behind, 2021 June 15; UA256.000292; 1 Digital Object(s); 837 Kilobytes
    - Take a Bite of Freedom, 2021 June 15; UA256.000293; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.03 Megabytes
      Oregon; Prisoners as artists -- United States; pen and ink drawings
  - Garcia, Michael, 2021 May 14; UA256.000294
    - America's Justice System, 2021 May 14; UA256.000295; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.40 Megabytes
  - Garrison, Joshua, 2021 May 14; UA256.000296; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - My Awakening, 2021 May 14; UA256.000297; 1 Digital Object(s); 184 Kilobytes
    - Inspirational nightmares, 2021 May 14; UA256.000298; 1 Digital Object(s); 99 Kilobytes
    - Reverberations, 2021 May 14; UA256.000299; 1 Digital Object(s); 47 Kilobytes
    - The Ghost in all of us, 2021 May 14; UA256.000300; 1 Digital Object(s); 719 Kilobytes
  - Giesa, John, 2021 May 14; UA256.000301
    - My Prayer, 2021 May 14; UA256.000302; 1 Digital Object(s); 419 Kilobytes
  - Ronin Samurai Against Ignorance, 2021 May 15; UA256.000303; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Man on Fire, 2021 May 15; UA256.000304; 1 Digital Object(s); 306 Kilobytes
    - Speak Life, 2021 May 15; UA256.000305; 1 Digital Object(s); 303 Kilobytes
    - The sweetness of a quiet moment, 2021 May 15; UA256.000306; 1 Digital Object(s); 41 Kilobytes
    - Justice is Blind, 2021 May 15; UA256.000307; 1 Digital Object(s); 77 Kilobytes
    - Freedom, 2021 May 15; UA256.000308; 1 Digital Object(s); 71 Kilobytes
    - Ebi Ni Mo Fi Okan, 2021 May 15; UA256.000309; 1 Digital Object(s); 75 Kilobytes
    - Mind...Trap, 2021 May 15; UA256.000310; 1 Digital Object(s); 60 Kilobytes
    - I am that Guy, 2021 May 15; UA256.000311; 1 Digital Object(s); 103 Kilobytes
    - And I'm a better man for it, 2021 May 15; UA256.000312; 1 Digital Object(s); 487 Kilobytes
  - Grady, Ferris E., Jr., 2021 June 12; UA256.000313; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Convicted in the Womb, 2021 June 12; UA256.000314; 1 Digital Object(s); 659 Kilobytes
  - Grady, Gus, Jr., circa 2021; UA256.000315; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 53)
    Missouri; Prisoners as artists -- United States
    - Old Cowboy, circa 2021; UA256.000316; 1 Digital Object(s); 23.3 Megabytes
      Missouri; Prisoners as artists -- United States; charcoal drawings
    - Young Aretha Franklin, circa 2021; UA256.000317; 1 Digital Object(s); 23.3 Megabytes
    - Praying Hands, circa 2021; UA256.000318; 1 Digital Object(s); 32.3 Megabytes
  - Grantley, Derrick, 2021 June 6; UA256.000319; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Justice isn't Blind, 2021 June 6; UA256.000320
      Florida; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Poetry
    - Nightmares of Slavery, 2021 June 6; UA256.000321
    - Does Anybody Care, 2021 June 6; UA256.000322
    - Quarantine Wonders, 2021 June 6; UA256.000323
    - Do you hear me?, 2021 June 6; UA256.000324
  - Gray, Marcos, circa 2021; UA256.000325
    - Poetic Tears, circa 2021; UA256.000326
    - Left Peace, circa 2021; UA256.000327
    - Eternal Life, circa 2021; UA256.000328
    - The Omen, circa 2021; UA256.000329
    - Forever & A Day, circa 2021; UA256.000330
    - Asylum, circa 2021; UA256.000331
  - Gray, Rahim, 2021 July 2; UA256.000332
    - I Am a Revolutionary, 2021 July 2; UA256.000333
      Prisoners as artists -- United States; acrylic paintings (visual works)
  - Griffin, Jeffery R., 2021 May 26; UA256.000334; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Here's to Fifty Years, 2021 May 26; UA256.000335
    - Serum Soliloquy, 2021 May 26; UA256.000336
    - Shining Starr, 2021 May 26; UA256.000337
    - Sunshine and Rain, 2021 May 26; UA256.000338
    - Reflections, 2021 May 26; UA256.000339
  - Grimsley, Robert, 2021 June 9; UA256.000340; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - COVID the Communist Bat, 2021 June 9; UA256.000341
  - Gonzalez, Reinaldo, circa 2021; UA256.000967
    - Re-sentencing, circa 2021; UA256.000968
    - Hero's, circa 2021; UA256.000969
    - Dear momma, circa 2021; UA256.000970
    - Changes, circa 2021; UA256.000971
    - After His Prison Time, circa 2021; UA256.000972
      Washington (State); Prisoners as artists -- United States; Poetry
  - Gross, Richard, 2021 June 8 -- 2021 June 9; UA256.000342; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - Injustice, 2021 June 9; UA256.000343
    - Big Brass Keys, 2021 June 9; UA256.000344
    - A Personal Narrative Regarding the Death Penalty, 2021 June 9; UA256.000345
    - Age Appropriate, 2021 June 9; UA256.000346; 1 Digital Object(s); 2.12 Megabytes
    - Sincerely, 2021 June 8; UA256.000347
    - Darkness Denied, 2021 June 8; UA256.000348
    - Caged Creatures, 2021 June 8; UA256.000349
    - A poem on poetry, 2021 June 8; UA256.000350
    - Nothing Soft in Prison, 2021 June 8; UA256.000351
    - Fire, 2021 June 8; UA256.000352
    - Aroma, 2021 June 8; UA256.000353
  - Grosso, Joe, 2021 May 25; UA256.000354; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Now This is Man, 2021 May 25; UA256.000355; 1 Digital Object(s); 2.64 Megabytes
  - Guerra, Gustavo, 2021 June 24 -- 2021 September 8; UA256.000356; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - Life(sentence), 2021 June 24; UA256.000357
    - Rashly Said, 2021 June 24; UA256.000358
    - Listen, 2021 June 24; UA256.000359
    - Disrespect, 2021 June 24; UA256.000360
  - Guzenhauser, Ben, circa 2021; UA256.000361
    - Nobody Knows, circa 2021; UA256.000362
    - Closer, circa 2021; UA256.000363
    - Break Free, circa 2021; UA256.000364
    - My Days, circa 2021; UA256.000365
    - Weights & Pulleys, circa 2021; UA256.000366
    - Identity Matters, circa 2021; UA256.000367
  - Haddock, Gary, circa 2021; UA256.000368
    - Labyrinth, circa 2021; UA256.000369; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.40 Megabytes
    - Landscapes Lesson 12, circa 2021; UA256.000370; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.40 Megabytes
    - Dude Where'd You Leave Your COVID-19, circa 2021; UA256.000371; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.40 Megabytes
  - Hall, Shawn, circa 2021; UA256.000372
    - How Prison has affected me, circa 2021; UA256.000373
      New York (State); Prisoners as artists -- United States; Essays
  - Hamblin, Rodney, circa 2021; UA256.000374
    - The Game, circa 2021; UA256.000375
    - When we met, circa 2021; UA256.000376
    - Give a chance, circa 2021; UA256.000377
    - Prison Time, circa 2021; UA256.000378
    - When you left, circa 2021; UA256.000379
  - Hanrahan, Adam J., circa 2021; UA256.000380; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - Social Reject, circa 2021; UA256.000381
    - The Hermit, circa 2021; UA256.000382
    - The Rising Pasan, circa 2021; UA256.000383
    - Time is One, circa 2021; UA256.000384
    - Demirgus Test, circa 2021; UA256.000385
    - Rock Bottom, circa 2021; UA256.000386; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.64 Megabytes
  - Harmon, Zachary, circa 2021; UA256.000387
    - Eye and owl, circa 2021; UA256.000388; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.4 Megabytes
      California; Prisoners as artists -- United States; linocuts (prints)
  - Harrison, Bryant, 2021 May 20 -- 2021 September 4; UA256.000389; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - The Forbidden Zone, 2021 May 20; UA256.000390
    - Overcome, 2021 May 20; UA256.000391
    - A Long Journey, 2021 May 20; UA256.000392; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.84 Megabytes
  - Higgins, Morgan, circa 2021; UA256.000393
    - Project Paint, circa 2021; UA256.000394; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.40 Megabytes
    - Lesson 6 Project Paint, circa 2021; UA256.000395; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.40 Megabytes
  - Hill, Charles, 2021 May 26; UA256.000396; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - Liberation, 2021 May 26; UA256.000397
    - Questionable Freedom, 2021 May 26; UA256.000398
    - A Dog's Eye View, 2021 May 26; UA256.000399
    - Untitled essay, 2021 May 26; UA256.000400
      Illinois; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Essays
  - Hinds, Timothy, circa 2021; UA256.000401
    - Untitled story, circa 2021; UA256.000402
  - Hindson, Brian, 2021 May 16; UA256.000403; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - Dove, 2021 May 16; UA256.000404; 1 Digital Object(s); 2.16 Megabytes
      Texas; Prisoners as artists -- United States; acrylic paintings (visual works)
  - Holtzer, Kevin, 2021 May 24; UA256.000405; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 64)
    - If, 2021 May 24; UA256.000406
    - Life Sentence, 2021 May 24; UA256.000407
  - Hong, Suliva S., 2021 June 24; UA256.000408; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 65)
    - Casket or them Chains, 2021 June 24; UA256.000409
    - Illusions, 2021 June 24; UA256.000410
    - No Justice No Peace, 2021 June 24; UA256.000973
    - Pray for Me, 2021 June 24; UA256.000974
  - Horton, Phillip R., circa 2021; UA256.000411
    - The Reasonable Man?, circa 2021; UA256.000412
    - Shadows and Puppets, circa 2021; UA256.000413
    - Who am I, circa 2021; UA256.000414
    - Den of The Mad, circa 2021; UA256.000415
    - Beneath The Frozen Moon, circa 2021; UA256.000416
  - Howard, Isschar, circa 2021; UA256.000417
    - Arraignment, circa 2021; UA256.000418
    - The Reason, circa 2021; UA256.000419
    - Welcome to U.S.A. Inferno, circa 2021; UA256.000420
  - Hubbard, Darneil, 2021 May 12; UA256.000421; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 66)
    20 years from date of creation.
    - Waiting on a Come Up, 2021 May 12; UA256.000422
    - My Story, 2021 May 12; UA256.000423
  - Hudgen, Tre'Arra, 2021 June 29 -- 2021 September 9; UA256.000424; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 67)
    - My Prison Life, 2021 June 29; UA256.000425
  - Hudgins, Justyn, 2021 October 2 -- 2021 September 7; UA256.000426; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 68)
    - Untitled Essay, 2020 October 2; UA256.000427; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.04 Megabytes
  - Hughes, Steven D., 2021 June 10; UA256.000428; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 69)
    - Thoughts, 2021 June 10; UA256.000429
  - Humphrey, Savannah, 2021 May 19; UA256.000430
    - Effects of my Incarceration, 2021 May 19; UA256.000431
  - Hunt, Charles, 2021 May 20; UA256.000432
    - Untitled Essay, 2021 May 20; UA256.000433
  - Iglehart, Sharon. M.D., 2021 June 23; UA256.000434; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 70)
    - Sometimes it Snows in April, 2012 June 23; UA256.000435; 1 Digital Object(s); 2.85 Megabytes
      Texas; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Short stories
  - Adril Blue, 2021 June 26; UA256.000436
    - Life's cast away, 2021 June 26; UA256.000437
    - Turning point, 2021 June 26; UA256.000438
    - The Multiverse Theory of Freewill, 2021 June 26; UA256.000439; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.23 Megabytes
  - Jackson, Jevon, 2021 May 3; UA256.000440; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 71)
    Wisconsin; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Poetry
    - Sixteen, 2021 May 3; UA256.000441
      Wisconsin; Prisoners as artists -- United States
    - Prison Guard, 2021 May 3; UA256.000442
    - From A Cold, Dark Room, 2021 May 3; UA256.000443
    - re-released, 2021 May 3; UA256.000444
    - What I've Seen, 2021 May 3; UA256.000445
    - Bloom, 2021 May 3; UA256.000446
  - Jackson, Miranda, 2021 May 21; UA256.000447
    - Untitled Essay, 2021 May 21; UA256.000448
  - Jacobs, Shaquan, circa 2021; UA256.000449
    - No Letting Go, circa 2021; UA256.000450
    - Thank You Dad, circa 2021; UA256.000451
    - A Black Person's Reality: The board game that's not a game!, circa 2021; UA256.000452
      Massachusetts; Prisoners as artists -- United States; digital art (visual works)
  - Jantz, Mark, 2021 June 10; UA256.000453; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 72)
    - Silence, 2021 June 10; UA256.000454
    - Dear Strange Spot on the Ceiling Above My Bunk, 2021 June 10; UA256.000455
  - Jennings, Pooja Pari, 2020 May 17; UA256.000456
    - Just One Friend, 2020 May 17; UA256.000457
  - Johnson, Harold, 2021 June 11; UA256.000458; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 73)
    Oklahoma; Prisoners as artists -- United States
    - Resentencing, 2021 June 11; UA256.000459; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.90 Megabytes
      Oklahoma; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Essays
  - Johnson, Ladrina, circa 2021; UA256.000460
    - Freedom Granted, circa 2021; UA256.000461
    - All Boxed In, circa 2021; UA256.000462
  - LoveJones, 2021 June 25; UA256.000463; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 74)
    - Life, 2021 June 25; UA256.000464
    - Mercy, 2021 June 25; UA256.000465
    - Lost, 2021 June 25; UA256.000466
    - Apologetic, 2021 June 25; UA256.000467
  - Jones, Forrest, 2020 July 27; UA256.000468
    - The Black Man in America Today: A perspective from a Black man, 2020 July 27; UA256.000469
  - Joyce, Jeremy, 2021 May 29; UA256.000470; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Paris in the Winter, 2021 May 29; UA256.000471
  - Kenyon, Bruce L., Sr., 2021 June 29; UA256.000472; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 76)
    - Grow Where You're Planted, 2021 June 29; UA256.000473; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.09 Megabytes
  - Key, Kenneth M., 2021 June -- 2021 September 01; UA256.000474; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 77)
    - What Happens to a Man Once He Hits to the Prison, 2021 June; UA256.000475; 1 Digital Object(s); 3.24 Megabytes
    - Mass Incarceration =, 2021 June; UA256.000476
    - The Other Death Penalty LWOP, 2021 June; UA256.000477
    - Just Masturbation, 2021 June; UA256.000478
    - Incarceration what does it mean?, 2021 June; UA256.000479; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.14 Megabytes
    - ReSentencing Means, 2021 June; UA256.000480; 1 Digital Object(s); 113 Kilobytes
    - Children of the Damn, 2021 June; UA256.000481; 1 Digital Object(s); 22.6 Megabytes
      Illinois; Prisoners as artists -- United States; acrylic paintings (visual works)
    - A Hand up-, 2021 June; UA256.000482; 1 Digital Object(s); 22.6 Megabytes
    - Eyes on you?, 2021 June; UA256.000483; 1 Digital Object(s); 22.6 Megabytes
    - ReSentencing (A Prison Solution), 2021 June; UA256.000484; 1 Digital Object(s); 22.9 Megabytes
  - Kinnison, Derek, circa 2021; UA256.000485
    - Sentencing Day, circa 2021; UA256.000486
      Nebraska; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Short stories
    - Among the Quiet of a Room, circa 2021; UA256.000487
      Nebraska; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Poetry
  - Kinzer, Aaron M., circa 2021; UA256.000488; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 78)
    - Season Pass, circa 2021; UA256.000489
    - That Time, circa 2021; UA256.000490
  - Landgraf, Susan, circa 2021; UA256.000491
    Washington (State); Prisoners as artists -- United States
    - Looking to Get Out, circa 2021; UA256.000492
    - Short History of Cummins, circa 2021; UA256.000493
    - Murders in the Joints, circa 2021; UA256.000494
    - After the Visits, circa 2021; UA256.000495
  - Latre, Jessica, 2021 June 28; UA256.000496; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 79)
    - Forgive My Lord, 2021 June 28; UA256.000497
    - Someday, 2021 June 28; UA256.000498
    - Light, 2021 June 28; UA256.000499
  - Juniper Steele, 2021 June 20 -- 2021 September 08; UA256.000500; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 80)
    - It's all hard, 2021 June 20; UA256.000501; 1 Digital Object(s); 18.8 Megabytes
      Oregon; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Pencil drawings
    - Unexpected Blessings, 2021 June 20; UA256.000502; 1 Digital Object(s); 26.9 Megabytes
    - All of This Before My Eyes, 2021 June 20; UA256.000503; 1 Digital Object(s); 26.7 Megabytes
  - Lee, Christopher, circa 2021; UA256.000504
    - Fuel the Fire Within, circa 2021; UA256.000505; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.20 Megabytes
  - LoBue, Philip Luke, 2021 May 29; UA256.000506; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 81)
    - Absence, 2021 May 29; UA256.000507
    - The colors of a man, 2021 May 29; UA256.000508
  - Lopp, Joshua, 2021 May 23; UA256.000509; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 82)
    - Criminal Justice Reform, 2021 May 23; UA256.000510
  - Lucas, Troy, circa 2021; UA256.000511
    - Let Freedom Ring, circa 2021; UA256.000512; 1 Digital Object(s); 19.8 Megabytes
  - Lyon, Edward B., Jr., 2021 May 22; UA256.000513; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 83)
    - The Incomplete Memoir of a Texas Prisoner, 2021 May 22; UA256.000514
    - New Wave Slaves in Chinese Boots, 2021 May 22; UA256.000515
  - Maraglino, Dorothy, 2021 May 17; UA256.000516; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 84)
    - A Prisoner's Tear, 2021 May 17; UA256.000517
    - *A Chance to Go Home*, 2021 May 17; UA256.000518
    - Prison Illusion, 2021 May 17; UA256.000519
    - Broken, 2021 May 17; UA256.000520
    - Prisoner's Paradox, 2021 May 17; UA256.000521
    - Don't Mind, 2021 May 17; UA256.000522
    - *A New Approach To Crime Prevention*, 2021 May 17; UA256.000523
  - "Iam" Infinite Immortal Warrior, 2016 February 12 -- 2020 October 17; UA256.000524; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 85)
    - R.A.C.E.: Really, Another, Clear, Excuse, 2016 February 12; UA256.000525
    - R.I.O.T.: Reflect, Innovate, Overcome, Triumph, 2018 March 15; UA256.000526
    - Everything I will be, 2019 November 28; UA256.000527
    - Origins, 2020 September 2; UA256.000528
    - Intimacy: In to me u see, 2020 October 17; UA256.000529
  - Martinez, Daniel, circa 2021; UA256.000530; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 86)
    Arizona; Prisoners as artists -- United States
    - True beauty is dangerous, 2021 June 13; UA256.000531; 1 Digital Object(s); 107 Megabytes
      Arizona; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Pencil drawings
    - Lion visual art, circa 2021; UA256.000532; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.26 Megabytes
  - Marvin, Jonathan, circa 2021; UA256.000533
    - Dragonfly visual art, circa 2021; UA256.000534
      California; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Sculpture (visual works)
  - Mason, Glen, 2021 June 4; UA256.000535; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 87)
    - Alone, 2021 June 4; UA256.000536
  - Mathes, J.D., circa 2021; UA256.000537
    - The Long Road to Fresno, circa 2021; UA256.000538
  - McCarley, Stephanie, 2021 May 22; UA256.000539
    - She, 2021 May 22; UA256.000540
  - McCarron, Karen, circa 2021; UA256.000541
    - On Maggie Shelledy's Rhetorical Agency and Resilient Dwelling, circa 2021; UA256.000542
  - Jerusalem, 2021 June 18; UA256.000543; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 88)
    - A Broken Man, 2021 June 18; UA256.000544
    - A Bunch of Questions, 2021 June 18; UA256.000545
    - Untitled poem, 2021 June 18; UA256.000546
  - McKee, Melissa, circa 2021; UA256.000547
    - A Different Sort of Citizen, circa 2021; UA256.000548
      Washington (State); Prisoners as artists -- United States; Essays
    - To a Prison Dentist, circa 2021; UA256.000549
    - I'm Not Crying, You're Crying, circa 2021; UA256.000550
    - Happy Birthday, Or Whatever, circa 2021; UA256.000551
    - How to Graduate College: Unabridged Version, circa 2021; UA256.000552
    - How to Forget How to Live, circa 2021; UA256.000553
  - McKnight, Marlon, 2021 June 30; UA256.000554; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 89)
    Indiana; Prisoners as artists -- United States
    - On the inside looking out, 2021 June 30; UA256.000555
      Indiana; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Poetry
    - Back in the day, 2021 June 30; UA256.000556
  - McManus, Joseph, 2021 June 25; UA256.000557
    - The Garden Sleeps, 2021 June 25; UA256.000558
  - McPhail, Marc Joseph, 2021 May 25; UA256.000559; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 90)
    - I Can't Breathe, 2021 May 25; UA256.000560
  - Meadows, Wanda, 2021 June 2; UA256.000561
    - Thankfulness, 2021 June 2; UA256.000562; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.28 Megabytes
      Florida; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Collages (visual works)
    - Portrait collage, 2021 June 2; UA256.000563; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.24 Megabytes
    - Please Will Thy Forgive Me?, 2021 June 2; UA256.000564; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.13 Megabytes